const decks = {
  deck1: [
    {
      cardFront: 'deck1 1',
      cardBack: 'deck1 1',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck1 2',
      cardBack: 'deck1 2',
    },
  ],
  deck2: [
    {
      cardFront: 'deck2 1',
      cardBack: 'deck2 1',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck2 2',
      cardBack: 'deck2 2',
    },
  ],
  deck3: [
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 1',
      cardBack: 'deck3 1',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 2',
      cardBack: 'deck3 2',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 3',
      cardBack: 'deck3 3',
    },
  ],
  deck4: [
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 1',
      cardBack: 'deck3 1',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 2',
      cardBack: 'deck3 2',
    },
    {
      cardFront: 'deck3 3',
      cardBack: 'deck3 3',
    },
  ],
};

export default decks;
